Go directly to:

* Products
    
    Wholesale

    Rural

    Quick links

* Knowledge
    
    RaboResearch

    Food & Agribusiness

    Countries and Regions

    Rabobank Knowledge

* Support
    
    Our support

* About us
    
    Who we are

    Our impact

Search 

Search

Login

1. [Home](https://www.rabobank.com/)

Privacy and your personal data
==============================

You share all kinds of personal data with us, for example, when you visit our website, apply for a job, or conduct transactions with us. We process this data with care and would like to inform you about this clearly and straightforwardly.

Frequently asked questions about our Privacy Statement
------------------------------------------------------

### What is personal data and from whom do we process personal data?

Personal data is data that directly or indirectly identifies you. If you are a customer (or customer representative) of Rabobank or you make contact with us, we collect and process your personal data. For example, we may process your data if you leave your name and e-mail address on our website.

We process the personal data of the following persons:

Customers & potential customers: we process the personal data of customers and their representatives, but also of persons who show an interest in us, our products, and services. Business partners: we process personal data from people who are associated with a company or organization with which we have, want to get, or have had a relationship. Job applicants: we process the personal data of job applicants who have applied for a position at Rabobank.

### What does processing mean?

Processing means anything that we can do with data, such as collection, recording, storage, alteration, organization, use, disclosure, transfer, or deletion.

### For what purposes can we process your personal data?

We process your data for various purposes. In the Privacy Statement for your region or location, you can read exactly the purposes and legal basis for which we process your personal data. For example, we process personal data to meet our legal obligations (such as Anti Money Laundering, Know Your Customer, or fraud prevention activities) or we process your data because you apply for a position at Rabobank.

### Who do we share your personal data with?

We only share your data with others if there is a legitimate reason or a legal obligation for us to do so. For example, we might share your personal with other divisions within the Rabobank Group (e.g. if you do business with the bank in multiple locations or you make use of multiple products offered by the bank). Additionally, we might share your data with parties outside of Rabobank Group, such as the Government/Regulatory bodies or third parties who assist us in the provision of services.

### What rights do you have?

When we use your data, you have certain rights. You have the right to:

be informed – about how and why we process your data have access – to the data that we have about you correction – of incorrectly recorded data erasure – of data where we no longer have a legal basis to process it object – to the processing of your data automated decision making – you have the right not to have decisions made about you that have a legal or similar impact, solely based on automated means data portability – to obtain your data in a machine-readable format (only applicable where the EU General Data Protection Regulation applies).

### Do you have a question or complaint about the processing of your personal data?

Do you have a general question or complaint about the processing of personal data? Then contact the persons identified in the relevant Privacy Statement to submit your question or complaint.

Are you dissatisfied with how your question or complaint has been handled by us? Then you can contact our Data Protection Officer. Of course, you can also submit your question or complaint to your Data Protection Authority or the Dutch Data Protection Authority which oversees Rabobank Group as a whole.

### How do we protect your personal data?

At Rabobank, we have implemented Binding Corporate Rules, the Rabobank Privacy Codes. This means that all entities, in which Rabobank Group has a controlling interest, must meet minimum standards in relation to the collection and processing of personal data of its clients and employees. As an organization, we are committed to taking the necessary organizational and technical measures to protect your personal data when we process it and share that data with third parties.

In addition, all Rabobank employees are subject to confidentiality obligations, meaning that you can trust that your data will not be shared improperly or unlawfully.

### What can you do to protect your data?

Rabobank has committed to protecting your data, However, we also recommend several actions you can take to protect your data:

Install necessary software on your electronic devices (e.g. phones, computers & tablets) to protect their security (e.g. anti-virus, anti-spyware, and firewall software). Do not leave your unlocked devices or security tokens unattended. Protect your secure access to systems by logging out when they are not in use and storing passwords securely (e.g. via a secure password manager). Do not share your login information with other people. Pay attention to unusual activity such as phishing (via email, text, or call) or security breach alerts. Rabobank will never ask you to provide your password or PIN to validate your identity when contacting you via telephone, email, or text.

### What has changed in our latest Privacy Statement?

Prior to November 2020 we uploaded on generic Privacy Statement applicable to most of Rabobank’s Wholesale & Rural divisions. Going forward we will provide a Privacy Statement at least per region and where required we may also provide a country-specific Privacy Statement.

More about Privacy
------------------
